{
    "subject": "resource/Bronze_Head_of_Hypnos_from_Civitella_d'Arna",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Bronze Head of Hypnos",
    "human_readable": "The name of the Bronze Head of Hypnos from Civitella d'Arna is Bronze Head of Hypnos.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9882457256317139,
            "question": "What is the name of the Bronze Head of Hypnos from Civitella d'Arna?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9046227335929871,
            "question": "What material is the Bronze Head of Hypnos made from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.901436448097229,
            "question": "Is there a known artist who created the Bronze Head of Hypnos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9003403782844543,
            "question": "From where does the Bronze Head of Hypnos originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8827975392341614,
            "question": "Is 'Bronze Head of Hypnos' a sculpture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7526916265487671,
            "question": "How is the Bronze Head of Hypnos displayed today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7224190831184387,
            "question": "What period does the Bronze Head of Hypnos likely belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.656766414642334,
            "question": "Who is Hypnos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5546451807022095,
            "question": "Are there any other notable artifacts from Civitella d'Arna?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.020763730630278587,
            "question": "What are some common themes depicted in ancient Greek sculptures?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of the Bronze Head of Hypnos from Civitella d'Arna is Bronze Head of Hypnos.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2385_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other notable artifacts from Civitella d'Arna?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2385_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Hypnos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2385_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What period does the Bronze Head of Hypnos likely belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2385_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2385_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2385_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2385_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2385_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2385_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2385_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2385_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2385_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2385_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2385_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation result:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the statement \"The name of the Bronze Head of Hypnos from Civitella d'Arna is Bronze Head of Hypnos\" is supported by the documents. The various references to \"Bronze head of Hypnos\", \"Head of Hypnos\", and other similar names in the context information confirm this statement."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents describe a bronze head of Hypnos, and it specifically mentions that this piece was found at Civitella d'Arno. Therefore, the statement that the name of the Bronze Head of Hypnos from Civitella d'Arna is \"Bronze Head of Hypnos\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}